Guide to the Carl Geiser Papers ALBA.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Biographical Files
  - Berman, Leopold, undated, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Berserie, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Bessie, Alvah, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Blair, John Clarence, undated, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Bortz, Louis, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Bourisko, Andrew, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Braley, Roger Lancaster, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Brown, Tom, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Browne, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Burmas, Charlie, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Cameron, James, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Cane, Larry, undated, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Carney, William P., undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - de la Casa-Barro, Joseph and Andrew, undated, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Castle, Guy, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Chase, Homer Bates, undated, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Chase, Van Rensalaer, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Colver, Robert C., undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Conway, Maurice, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Cunningham, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Dabelko, Steve, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Dahl, Whitey, 1936-1983 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Dallard, Randolph (Norwegian), undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Delgado, Carmelo, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Delich, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Diaz, Ricardo, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Dobrowolski, N., undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Domnauer, Olaf, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Doran, Dave, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Doran, Lawrence Faut, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Doriot, Jacques, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Dorland, Norman, undated, 1938, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Dougher, Joseph, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Dykstra, Matthew, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Earle, Howard, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Ecker, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Edwards, Frank: “Portrait of An Irish Anti-Fascist” by Manus O’Riorden, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Elendiuk, Nick, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Epailly, Raymond, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Feld, Herman, undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Fender, Francis Edwin, undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Finnick, Eugene R., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Firmin, Charles Edward, undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Franco, Manuel Garcia, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Frohman, Raleigh, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Gandall, William, undated, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Garcia, Enrique, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Geiser, Carl, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Gerhardt, Julius, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Gibbon, Dave, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Giler, Henry, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gonzalez, Manuel Casal, undated, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Gorgan, Arthur Q., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Grachow, Leo, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Graeber, Kenneth, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Grant, Samuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Grant, Walter Fairbanks, undated, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Graver, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Grigas, Joseph, undated, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Groden, Dan, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Gradzki, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gurko, Maurice, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hall, Charles Alfred, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hannigan, Walter R., undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Harris, Sidney, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Harris, Steve, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hausman, Carl, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Heinricker, Stanley, undated, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hesketh, Harry, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Higgins, Jimmy (Canada): Subject of Manuel Alvarez’s The Tall Soldier, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Higgins, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Hilton, Percy, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Hodge, Edward, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Holoppainen, Eno, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Howard, Ramon Epailly, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Jacobs, Edward Deyo, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Johnson, John G., undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Keller, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kleiman, Harry, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kleinman, Joseph, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Kneshl, Miloslav, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Kowalski, Arthur, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Kraxner, Joseph, undated, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Kunslitch, Alex, undated, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Lardner, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Leisorowitz, Sol, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lemke, Otto, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lerner, Bernard Morris, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lerner, Sol, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Levy, Bert Yank, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Loak, Samuel C., undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Logan, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Lopez, Herman (Jules), undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Lorson, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Love, Vaughn, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - MacEachran (McEachron), Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Madis, Pietr, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Madsen, Nils, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Mail, Jack, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Maki, Martin, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Mandel, Emanuel (Manny), undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Mangolic, Anthony, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Manning, Robert, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Markowitz, Sam, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Markowski, George, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Martin, Fredericka, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Marttila, Helge, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Megquire, Henry, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Mennel, Morris, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Merriman, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Miller, Fred Ralph, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Miller, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Moon, Jimmy, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Mooney, Paul Andrew, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Morales, Mario, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Moscowitz, Ignatz, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Murphy, Roger, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Neafus, Ralph, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Neri, Deno, undated, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Nicolau, Ramon, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Norris, Len, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Opara, Rudolph, undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Ornitz, Lou, undated, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Paivo, Jules, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Panaszevicz, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Pardo, Iglesias Destrye (D.P. Iglesias), undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Parker, Max, undated, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Parks, Johnny, undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Pick, Robert, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Polansky, Sam, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Poling, Eugene, undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Pringle, Claude, undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Raacke, Peter, undated, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Ransel, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Reed, Bob, undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Riffe, Carl, undated, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Rifkin, Irving, undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Robles, Coco (Francesco), undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Romer, Sam, undated, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Rosenblatt, Sidney, undated, 1978, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Rubin, Irving, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Rutherford, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Ryan, Frank, undated, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Sancho, Amelio, undated (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Sanjanoes, Louis, undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Sanjenis, Sergio, undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Scanlon, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Schachter, Phil, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Service, Elman, undated (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Shaker, Kenneth, undated (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Shapiro, Linn, undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Shields, Art, undated, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Shufer, Max, undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Skorupinski, Mischa, undated (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Skup, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Small, John (Jim), undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Smith, Harold, undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Stanley, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Steck, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Steinberg, Jack, undated (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Stix, Fred, undated (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Stojewa, Henry, undated (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Stone, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Suarez, Manuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Swanson, Samuel, undated (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Tabb, Herbert, undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Tenor, Leon, undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Thompson, Richard, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Ticer, Leo, undated (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Tobman, Morris, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Totis, Luigi, undated, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Townsen, Gus, undated (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Turner, Leo, undated (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Urbina, Caesar, undated (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Wallach, Hy, undated (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Walsh, Bernie, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Weber, Robert Rubin, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Weismayer, Josef, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Zarona, Walter, undated (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Ziegler, Albert, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 135)
- Series IV: Prisoners of the Good Fight: Drafts and Manuscripts
  - Appendices, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Synopses, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Seven: Questionnaire & Responses, undated, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Nine: Questionnaire & Responses, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Typescript: Incomplete: Chapters 1-4, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Typescript: Incomplete: Page 1-101, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Typescript: Incomplete: Page 102-258, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Introduction-Page 83, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 84-226, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 227-342, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 343-476, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 477-606, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 607-734, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 735-875, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Typescript: Version 1: Pages 876-906 and Epilogue, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Introduction-Page 83, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 84-231, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 232-354, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 355-468, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 469-612, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 613-744, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Typescript: Version 2: Pages 745-906, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Series V: Subject Files
  - Belchite: Americans Captured and Executed, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - British Veterans, undated, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for Peace and Democracy East and West, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - City College: Memorial to City College Volunteers, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Comision de Homenaje a las Brigadas Internacionales, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Consortium for Extra-Curricular Activities, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Diario de Burgos (photocopies), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Executions: Jarama Trucks, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary: New York University Commemorative Event, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Finnish Volunteers, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation: Funding Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Franco: Americans who Served in Support of, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Franco: Nationalist Party, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, undated, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: First Anniversary Commemorative Program (photocopy), undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: “Story of the Abraham Lincoln Battalion,” 1937 (photocopy), undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Geiser, Carl: “I Was in a Fascist Concentration Camp,” Young Communist(photocopy), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Geiser, Carl: "No Embargo on the Bill of Rights," Young Communist(photocopy), undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Geiser, Carl: “‘Silent Night, Holy Night’-In a Spanish Prison Camp, 1938,” New York Times, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - German Gestapo, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Hemingway: Veterans’ Commentary on For Whom the Bell Tolls, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hene International Mash Unit, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Ibarruri, Dolores, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - International Brigades Archives (Moscow), 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - International Brigades: Personnel, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - International Brigades: General Meeting Minutes, 1937 (photocopy) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - International Prisoners Reunion, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - “Jaily News" (partial photocopy of no. 15, p. 2, August 11, 1938; original of first page is in Vault) and Correspondence, 1938, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Kormes, Karl, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion of Canada, undated, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Maritime Workers Historical Society, undated, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Media Contacts, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Medical Personnel, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Medical Personnel: Polish, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Medical Issues, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Miranda de Ebro Tribute, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Monument to American Volunteers in Spain (Barcelona), undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Research Grant, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Nicaragua: O’Riordan, Manus (Irish Transportation & General Workers’ Union) Statement, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Prago, Albert: “A Visit With Eight Spanish Women”, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Prison: Beatings, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Prison: Communist Party Organizing in Camp, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Prison: General, undated, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Prison: Life and Experiences, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Prison: Visitors, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Prisoners: Aid and Support, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Prisoners: Americans Reported Captured, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Prisoners: British (includes correspondence with Bill Alexander), 1939, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Prisoners: British (includes correspondence with Tom Bloomfield, Bob Doyle, Dougal Eggar, Dave Goodman), 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Prisoners: Canadian, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Prisoners: Capture and Execution, undated, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Prisoners: Cuban, undated, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Prisoners: Dutch, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Prisoners: Escapes, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Prisoners: Exchange, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Prisoners: Food & Clothing, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Prisoners: French, undated, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Prisoners: General, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Prisoners: German, undated, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Prisoners: Hungarian, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Prisoners: Italian, undated, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Prisoners: Lists, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Prisoners: Norwegian, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Prisoners: Polish, 1940-1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Prisoners: Release, undated, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Prisoners: Release: Earl T. Crain (U.S. Foreign Service Officer), 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Prisoners: Swiss, undated, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Prisoners: Trials, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Prisoners of the Good Fight: Progress Reports, undated, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Prisoners of the Good Fight: Publication and Promotion, 1978-1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Red Cross: American and International, undated, 1938-1950, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Red Diaper Babies, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Repatriation of Americans: Louis Fischer Papers (photocopies), 1939, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Research: General Notes, undated, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Research Repository: Archivo Historico National (Salamanca), undated, 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Research Repository: Archivos del Ministerio de Asuntos Consulares (Madrid), undated, 1938-1940, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Research Repository: U.C. Berkeley, Bancroft Library, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Research Repository: Library of Congress, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Research Repository: National Archives, 1937-1938, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Return to Spain, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Robeson, Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sailing List: Passage to Spain (Annotated), undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - San Pedro de Cardeña, undated, 1938, 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - San Pedro de Cardeña: Christmas, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - San Pedro de Cardeña: Dutch Prisoners, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - San Pedro de Cardeña: French Prisoners, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - San Pedro de Cardeña: Italian Prisoners, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Spain: United States Foreign Relations and Policy, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Spain: Volunteers Return, 1979, 1983, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Spanish Civil War, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Spanish Civil War: American Aviators, undated, 1975-1990 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Spanish Civil War: American Participation: “For Whom the Bell Tolled” (photocopied from commemorative pamphlet), ca.1980 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Spanish Civil War: Anniversaries & Tributes (clippings), 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Spanish Civil War: Book and Film Reviews (clippings), 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Spanish Civil War: British Aviators, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Spanish Civil War: Chronology, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Spanish Civil War: Chronology, August 1936-April 1938, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Spanish Civil War: Chronology, May 1938-May 1939, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Spanish Civil War: Chronology, May 1939-February 1940, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Spanish Civil War: Communism (clippings), 1986 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Spanish Civil War: German Volunteers, undated, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Spanish Civil War: New York Times Coverage, 1937-1940 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Spanish Civil War: Postal History (correspondence with Ronald Shelley), 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Spanish Civil War: Press Coverage of American Volunteers and Prisoners (photocopies), 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Spanish Civil War: Prisoners and Prisons (clippings), undated, 1938-1939, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans (clippings), 1940-1989 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans: Annotated Version of Adolph Ross List, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Spanish Civil War: Veterans List, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Spanish Civil War Historical Society (VALB), undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Spanish Civil War Literature: Dartmouth College Symposium, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Tisa, John: The Palette and the Flame, Reviews and Advertisements, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1939, 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: El Salvador, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: Historical Commission News Briefs, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Veterans Rights, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Volunteer for Liberty: Background, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - West Coast Volunteer, Vol. 1, no. 5, June-July 1941 (photocopy), undated (Box 8, Folder 59)